<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><root><date> 08:44:23.42 </date> <title> poehl say far rate cut possibl sourc </title> <body> bundesbank presid karl otto poehl told close invest symposium west germani could cut lead interest rate unit state make similar move bank sourc say the sourc report poehl remark symposium duesseldorf last week organis deutsch bank Ag press repres invit the sourc speak separ say poehl told 200 banker repli question cut u. interest rate would give room match measur germani `` It definit hint low german interest rate say one banker attend symposium A bundesbank spokesman say central bank would comment report remark make privat meet but accord second sourc also declin identifi poehl comment see banker present direct pointer move central bank defend german industri addit revalu mark `` He say american drop interest rate bundesbank would also drop He say quit clearli second sourc say In repli question poehl also say half-point cut discount lombard rate januari 22 come u. have signal would prepar attend meet discus level dollar condit germani make move advanc sourc say ask american author could persuad cut german rate come bargain tabl earli last septemb one sourc quot poehl say No would n We check the pari meet group six industri nation take place exactli one month german cut rate poehl emphasis comment close talk central bank meet say financi market fulli realis signific pari session u. agreement stem fall valu dollar sourc say for first time particip summit agre fall dollar would harm world economi includ u. poehl say the sourc say tone poehl comment boost grow sentiment dollar would stabilis around current level intern central bank cooper one sourc say poehl remark also underlin fact bundesbank prepar accommod monetari polici order prevent slowdown west germani econom growth poehl bundesbank offici past stress german central bank direct respons growth sole concern combat inflat thi lead instanc introduct tighter monetari stanc begin decemb half-point cut rate late januari the sourc quot poehl say current overshoot german monetari target would directli respark inflat the bundesbank oblig react immedi whenev overshoot occur late data central bank money stock bundesbank main measur money suppli show measur grow pct januari outsid three six pct 1987 target share price rise activ trade today dealer report poehl remark coupl bullish outlook stock price deutsch symposium brought strong bargain hunt current low level </body></root>